hymnary.org 2011-05-30

# Privacy Policy | Hymnary.org

Because we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it, we have adopted this Privacy Policy. There are several Hymnary services that require the collection of information from you. These services include signing up with a user name and password to enable you to access community features. Other services may set cookies on your computer. 

**Our Use of "Cookies"**

Cookies are small bits of data that we send to your computer. They identify you as a Hymnary user and contain information regarding your Hymnary preferences.

The cookies are not used for tracking users outside the Hymnary Web site, and they are not accessible by third parties. 

**Web Site Traffic Information**

When you visit this or any Web site, information is available to the site on the pages you view, the time of your visit, the browser you are using, the address of the computer you visit from, and the address of the page you are coming from. We use this information internally only, to better understand user needs and preferences and make the Hymnary more useful. We do not share this information with third parties unless required by law, and we do not track Web sites you visit before or after you access the Hymnary.

**Our Use and Disclosure of Information**

The Hymnary will not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third parties. 

The Hymnary does not send unsolicited e-mail to users. Only users who have voluntarily joined an e-mail list such as the hymnal editors or have given permission to receive Hymnary announcements receive e-mail from the Hymnary. 

**Notification of Changes**

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to Hymnary or as we incorporate suggestions from our users. The Hymnary is not responsible for notifying users of changes to this policy.

We will post the amended Privacy Policy promptly on our Web site so that you can always review what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check the CCEL Web site at [www.hymnary.org/info/privacy.html](http://www.hymnary.org/info/privacy.html) for the current version of our Privacy Policy.
